contactmusic.com 2017-12-28

# Privacy Statement | Contactmusic.com

It is very important to us here at Contactmusic.com that your privacy is both protected and respected but we sometimes ask that you provide certain information so that we can provide our services to the highest possible standard.

This policy, along with our website terms of use <http://www.contactmusic.com/page/termsandconditions>, sets out how we may use the personal data that we collect from you.

You should read these terms of use carefully before using [www.contactmusic.com](http://www.contactmusic.com/) ("site") so that you are familiar with how we use your data. Please do not continue to use our site if you do not agree to these terms.

What information do we collect and why?

We may collect the following data from you:

1\. Information that you give us 

You are providing us with information by completing fields and forms on our site such as when you:

      \- register as a member of our site;

      \- participate in discussion boards;

      \- enter a competition, promotion or survey; and 

      \- report a problem with our site. 

If you wish to be included on our mailing list, you must provide us with your email address so that we can contact you with regular updates. If for any reason you change your mind and would like to be removed from the mailing list, you can unsubscribe by following the <http://www.contactmusic.com/info/atmosphere#unsubscribe_all> in the email or by emailing us at [hello@contactmusic.com](mailto:hello@contactmusic.com).

As well as your email address, we may well ask you to provide your name, address and phone number.

2\. Information we collect about you

When you visit our site, we may automatically collect certain pieces of information, such as details about your computer, including where available your IP address, operating system and connection speed. This helps us to make improvements to the performance of our site and improve your online experience.

Occasionally we may release statistical data about user trends to a third party but will not share individual information except where you have provided us with consent or in the case of lawful requirement.

3\. Information about your visit

The advertising companies that serve the ads on our site may use details about your visit to our site to display ads based on your interests. This does not include any of your personal details such as your name or email address. 

For more information on advertising, please visit [http://www.youradchoices.com](http://www.youradchoices.com/) and/or [http://www.iab.net](http://www.iab.net/).

How do we store your data?

We store your personal details in secure databases that can only be accessed by certain members of the company. 

Unfortunately, submitting information through the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site. Please be aware that any information that you submit to our site is done so at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

Where you have registered as a member and have chosen a password you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

More information

We may update this policy from time to time so we recommend that you revisit this page to familiarise yourself with the changes. 

If you wish to update your personal information or have any queries regarding this policy and our use of your personal information, please let us know by emailing [hello@contactmusic.com](mailto:hello@contactmusic.com).
